path.to 2012-10-28

# Path.To : Privacy Policy

Last updated: 7/30/2012

Path.To.com respects the privacy of personal information it receives in the course of our business. This policy expresses Path.To's commitment to maintain the privacy of personal information that is shared with us, outlines what types of personally identifiable information Path.To receives, and summarizes what we do with this personal information.

### Sources of Personal Information

Path.To is a provider of workforce optimization solutions, which include the processing of recruitment, candidate information for customers and their suppliers of recruiting, staffing and consulting services. Path.To receives personal information of candidates. Path.To also collects personal information voluntarily shared by persons through email correspondence or responses to inquiries on our website.

### Uses of Personal Information

Path.To uses personal information supplied to us solely for legitimate business purposes and to perform it’s services for which we have been contracted by our customers. Path.To uses personal information for such purposes as collecting and sorting resumes for position fulfillment, evaluation and assessment, recordkeeping, recruitment services, and for ourselves.

Path.To shares personal information supplied by our customers and You, only for the purpose of the services for which we were contracted. For example, Path.To may share resumes and applicant information of candidates submitted by such individual for submission to a customer. Path.To will otherwise maintain as confidential and not use or share personal information of individuals submitted by You. Path.To retains Your personal information so long as Your account is active.

Path.To will share personal information as required by law or regulation, or in cooperation with law enforcement investigations, civil or criminal subpoenas, or when required by court orders.

Path.To will not sell personal information to mailing lists or share personal information to those who would use it for marketing purposes.

### Security of Personal Information

Path.To employs physical, technical and operational security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, disclosure or alteration of personal information submitted to us. We are committed to keeping your personal information private and will continue to take steps to back up this commitment.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use the Path.To services. We use cookies to record current session information, but do not require permanent cookies.

### Updating and Correcting Personal Information

If You would like to review or modify Your personal information may contact us at [help@Path.To](mailto:help@path.to). We will make reasonable efforts to address your request.

### Children

Path.To does not knowingly collect personal information from children (13 yrs. or less). If Path.To becomes aware that any personal information has been submitted online that relates to a child, Path.To will immediately delete such information from our records.

### Further Information

Path.To has in place procedures for training employees in implementation of this Privacy Policy and disciplining them for failure to follow it. Path.To has in place internal procedures for periodically conducting objective reviews of compliance with our Privacy Policy. If you want to know more about our commitment to Privacy, please contact us at [privacy@path.to](mailto:privacy@path.to).
